

CONTACT

© Sudeshnapr126@gmail.c om, 9833931587

Mumbai, Maharashtra

EDUCATION

- PUNE
 BSc (Electronics)
 2003
- SYMBIOSIS COLLEGE –
 PUNE
 PGDBA (Finance)

2012

GURU NANAK COLLEGE
OF EDUCATION &
RESEARCH –
MUMBAI

B. Ed

2014

SNDT Women's University
MUMBAI
MSc (e-learning)
2020-22
(Sem 4)

SUDESHNA PRASAD

ASPIRING INSTRUCTIONAL DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

Currently, I am pursuing semester 4, MSc e-learning. Teaching is my passion. It is my eagerness to learn and apply it in teaching; to make learning a happy and effective experience. e-learning content development has opened a plethora of teaching-learning experiences. Apart from this, I am a traveler, amateur photographer, fitness enthusiast and a mother.

EXPERIENCE

SCIENCE TEACHER

(2014-2017)

Taught science in CBSE and ICSE schools in Mumbai

PRIVATE TUTOR

(2017-2022)

Taught science and mathematics in private classes in online and classroom. Developed digital learning material.

INTERNSHIP

worked as an intern in an NGO for 5 weeks. Earned the experience in curriculum mapping and content development for grade 1 to 12.

SKILLS

- Create lesson plan to achieve learner's objectives on the basis of Bloom's taxonomy.
- Learner engagement by application of teaching strategies
- Development of content by applying various tools like thinklink, quizlet, audacity, wavepad, html, photoshop, articulate 360 etc. Wide utility of google suite, MS suite. Created and hosted content on MOODLE.
- Multi lingual English, Hindi, Bengali, Marathi & French